Four friends. One trip. No luck.
Joy Ride is a comedy film directed by Adele Lim.
When Audrey's business trip to Asia goes sideways, she enlists the aid of Lolo, her irreverent, childhood best friend who also
happens to be a hot mess; Kat, her college friend turned Chinese soap star; and Deadeye, Lolo's eccentric cousin.
Their no-holds-barred, epic experience becomes a journey of bonding, friendship, belonging, and wild
debauchery that reveals the universal truth of what it means to know and love who you are.
Audrey, played by Ashley Park.
Lolo, played by Sherry Cola.
Kat, played by Stephanie Hsu.
Deadeye, played by Sabrina Wu.
Chao, played by Ronny Chieng.
Nai Nai Chen, played by Lori Tan Chinn.
Joy Ride is a 2023 American comedy film directed by Adele Lim, and
written by Cherry Chevapravatdumrong and Teresa Hsiao.
The film stars Ashley Park, Sherry Cola, Stephanie Hsu, and Sabrina Wu.
The film was announced in 2018 following a partnership deal between Point Grey
Pictures and Lionsgate, with Lim being confirmed as director in 2021.
The cast was announced between August and October of the same year, and
filming took place in British Columbia throughout the latter month.
Joy Ride had its world premiere at SXSW on March 17, 2023, and was released
in the United States on July 7, 2023, by Lionsgate Films.
It received positive reviews from critics and grossed $16 million.
The film explores themes of female friendship, adopted
child, woman director, asian american.
The tone is lighthearted.